Guide to the Kim Hoffmann Photograph Collection PR 77
New-York Historical Society
- Oversize Material
  - From Series I: Residential Commissions
    - Drosin, 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 162)
    - Everett, Dr. and Mrs. John R., 1965 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 163)
    - Mabardi, [1949-1957] (Offsite-box 9, Folder 164)
    - Melken Nursery, 1947 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 165)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1953 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 166)
    - Ullman, Mr. and Mrs. James Ramsey, 1947 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 167)
    - Miscellaneous prints, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 168)
  - From Series I: Commercial and Professional Commissions
    - Audrey [women's shop], 1955 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 169)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club, 1954 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 170)
    - Casual Air, 1951 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 171)
    - New Englander Motor Hotel - Greenwich, CT, 1960 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 172)
    - New Englander Motor Hotel - Westport, CT, ca. 1960 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 173)
    - Realty Associates, 1951 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 174)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson D., 1953 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 175)
    - Miscellaneous prints, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 176)
  - From Series I: Hoffmann and Heidrich Offices and Apartments
    - 225 East 57th Street, Apts. 3G and 3I, [1945-1949] (Offsite-box 9, Folder 177)
    - 208 East 73rd Street, 1957-1963 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 178-179)
  - From Series II. Trade Shows
    - National Home Furnishing Show, 1952 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 180)
    - National Home Furnishing Show, 1956 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 181)
  - From Series III. Product and Designer Files
    - Hugo copper door, 1946 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 182)
    - Plexiglass, 1940-1980 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 183)
    - Sax, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 184)
    - Miscellaneous prints, undated (Offsite-box 9, Folder 185)
  - From Series IV. Publications and Correspondence: Articles by Hoffman and Heidrich
    - Articles by Hoffman clippings, 1952-1963 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 186)
    - Articles by Hoffman and Heidrich in Display World, Dec. 1949-Oct. 1952 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 187)
    - Articles by Hoffman and Heidrich in Playthings, Sep. 1955 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 188)
    - Articles by Hoffman and Heidrich - Miscellaneous, 1951-1953 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 189)
  - From Series IV. Publications and Correspondence: Articles about Hoffmann and Heidrich
    - In Interiors & Industrial Design, Feb. 1946 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 190)
    - In Vogue, 1947-1952 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 191)
    - Miscellaneous, 1947-1970 (Offsite-box 10, Folder 192-193)
  - From Series V. Personal Photographs: Travel Photographs
    - Paris, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 194)
  - From Series V. Personal Photographs: Other Photographs
    - Miscellaneous prints, undated (Offsite-box 10, Folder 195)